Lamidi, Hassan Taiwo

Lagos, Nigeria. Tel: 08177135933

Email: hassanadefarati@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/taiwo1
GitHub: https://github.com/Taiolamz

Front End Developer with 2+ years' experience in web development using ReactJS. Collaborated with a group of developers and product managers in successfully developing topnotch software products. Also, possess the ability to work in an agile environment.

Experience

• **ZojaTech -** 9B, Akin-Ogunmade Davies Street, Gbagada Phase II, Lagos State.

Front-end Web Developer (July 2022– Current) Software Developer/NYSC (September 2021– July 2022)

Worked primarily as a frontend developer in contributing to the development of the Budget Management System for in-house and External Clients (Reactjs and Redux). Worked on projects such as revvex.io, and PMS (Procurement Management System).

• Greenland Hall Secondary School – Shode Street, Off Egbado Road, Dalemo, Ogun State.

Programming Tutor - Contract (February 2021 – September 2021)

Assisted learners in the development of software using Html, CSS, and JavaScript, and helped them learn how to maintain and fix codes in different formats. Also, help in managing the school's website.

• Chordels(Nig) Enterprises – 4, Alakuko Road, Owonikoko, Agbado, Lagos. Data Administrator (August 2019 – February 2020)

Administered and monitored the Data Management System to ensure quality and consistency in the organization.

• Obafemi Awolowo University (Computer Centre)

Technical Support Intern (March 2019 – August 2019)

Provided support to the school's system and facilities. Managed the students' portal. Contributed to the configuration of the hardware devices used for the schools' examinations.

Assisted in the running of the organization's computer systems, routers, and internet to ensure the users get the maximum benefit from them.

Also served as a help to the Human Resource Section of the Institution as part of my internship.

• Freelance

Graphics Designer (Sept 2017 – Dec 2019)

Worked Primarily as a graphics designer using tools such as Corel Draw, and Photoshop cs6. Designed banners, and flyers as a freelancer.

Education

Oduduwa University Ipetumodu, Osun State.

B.Sc. Computer Science - Second Class Upper (2016-2020)

This entails theories and the practical application of computer science. Learned about several computing principles and data structures. The primary implementation of the principles was in C++.

Greenland Hall Secondary School - *Shode Street, Off Egbado Road, Dalemo, Ogun State.* WASCCE 2010-2016.

Projects:

- BMS- Budget Management System called Revvex (Revvex.io) developed for companies such as Addax Petroleum, AIICO Capital using React and Redux
- PMS Procurement Management System Web page called Mance (Mance.io) using React
- MaketPlace Ecommerce Application
- Lagoon Hospital Web Application developed for Lagoon Hospital using React
- DSPro Digital Signage Pro. developed for companies such as AIICO

Skills

- HTML 5 (4 years' experience)
- CSS (4 years' experience) SCSS, Bootstrap.
- JavaScript (2 years' experience) React.js,
- ReduxJS, jQuery
- NodeJS (5 month's experience)
- MongoDB
- ExpressJS
- Postman (API Testing)
- SQL
- AWS
- Git (1+ year experience)
- SEO

Others.

- Debugging
- Research
- Collaboration
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Problem

Solving

• API testing

REFEREES

Dr Elijah Adegoke.

HOD, Computer Science. Oduduwa University Ipetumodu, Osun State. 08034198862.

Mr. Dare Adewuyi. Lead Software Developer. ZojaTech. 07038808765.